
const OCEANIA = [{
    id: 1,
    question: 'Australia',
    answer: 'Canberra',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: 'Fiji',
    answer: 'Suva',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: 'Kiribati',
    answer: 'Tarawa',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: 'Marshall Islands',
    answer: 'Majuro',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: 'Micronesia',
    answer: 'Palikir',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: 'Nauru',
    answer: 'Yaren District',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: 'New Zealand',
    answer: 'Wellington',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: 'Palau',
    answer: 'Ngerulmud',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: 'Samoa',
    answer: 'Apia',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: 'Tonga',
    answer: "Nuku'alofa",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question: 'Tuvalu',
    answer: 'Funafuti',
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: 'Vanuatu',
    answer: 'Port Vila',
  }
  ]

  export default OCEANIA;